thegamehomepage.com 2019-04-08

# FreeGames.org Privacy Policy | FreeGames.org

Here at FreeGames.org your privacy is important to us. That is why we have created this page to outline the information we collect and store about visitors to our website.

## Third Party Advertisements

FreeGames.org features adverts by third party vendors. Some of these vendors, for example Google, use cookies to improve the relevency of their adverts. For instance the DoubleClick cookie contains data regarding which websites you have visited and helps Google to understand which adverts are most relevent to you. You can opt out of this service here: <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>.

## Visitor Statistics

For our statistics FreeGames.org logs vistor pageviews and some limited information including the visitor country and internet browser. This enables us to see how the site is being used by our visitors. No personally identifiable information is recorded for this purpose.

## Rating Games

If you rate one of the games on our site your IP address will be logged. The sole purpose of this is to check that the same user doesn’t rate a game more than once.

## Email Enquiries

In order to use our contact form you must enter your name, email address and message. These details are forwarded to us in an email so that we can respond. They are not added to a database or stored anywhere else.

## Game Cookies

There are many games hosted on FreeGames.org that make the use of “cookies”. A cookie is a small file of information that the site can access again later on. The main way in which these are used is to save your progess in a game. If you close a page then return to it later on the information held in the cookie lets the game know where you left off so you can continue from that point. Cookies are only used on FreeGames.org to improve your experience of the site and they do not store personal information such as your name.

## Links to external websites

On some pages FreeGames.org may link to external websites. If you follow a link to another website we recomend that you also read their privacy policy. FreeGames.org assumes no responsibility if a problem occurs on an external website and disclaims any warranties expressed on any other domain.

## Questions/Complaints

If you have any questions or complaints about our privacy policy please contact us using [this form](https://freegames.org/contact/).
